他是一名医生，也是 健康医生组织的领袖之一。
Dr. Julio began collecting information himself,
当政府于 2015 年 停止发布官方的医疗数据时，
using an informal but coordinated system
朱利奥博士开始 自己收集这些信息，
of cell phone communications.
使用一种非正式但协调的
They track available personnel, medical supplies, mortality data,
手机通讯系统。
disease outbreaks;
他们追踪可用人员、 医疗物资、死亡率数据，
compile it into a report;
和疾病爆发，
and then share that on Twitter.
将其编写成报告，
He became our go-to expert on health care in Venezuela.
之后在推特上分享。
Luis Carlos Díaz,
他变成了我们首要的 委内瑞拉医疗专家。
a widely recognized journalist who reports acts of censorship
路易斯 · 卡洛斯 · 迪亚兹 （Luis Carlos Díaz），
and human rights violations suffered by the people of Venezuela,